感谢Rado告诉我们，选择一个适合的SDK版本的重要性。
Thanks Rado, for telling us about the importance of proper dessert selection.
现在让我们来选择SDK版本吧~
Let's choose our dessert now. At the current time,
到目前为止，在Google Play商店的%99的活跃设备都选择了2.3.3以上的SDK。
choosing Gingerbread covers 99% of the devices active on the Google Play store.
像地图、位置和Android支持库，
It's also the cutout for using Google Play services, for things like maps and
这也是使用Google Play服务的切入口。
location, and the Android support library. The support library package
支持库包提供在更高版本中添加UI的功能。
offers an implementation of UI features that were added in later releases.
但是现在我们可以在老版本平台上使用，像Android 2.3.3。
But now can be used on older versions of the platform, like Gingerbread.
我们选择SDK的最新版本是 API 10，因为它修复了API 9平台上面的bugs
We pick the latest version of Gingerbread at API level 10, because it contains
我们继续，单击下一步。
bug fixes that API level 9 doesn't have. Then we go ahead and click Next.
我们提供了一个模板列表，可以选择创建一个新的应用程序。
We're presented with a list of templates that we can choose from in order to create
好的，那么我们选择 Blank Activity with Fragment Template。
our new app. We're going to pick the Blank Activity with Fragment Template.
针对后台运行的上下文，activity是我们展示UI的表现层。
For background context, an activity serves as the presentation layer for our UI.
其中fragment是作为我们的页面逻辑的部分。
And the fragment within it represents a behavior or portion of the screen.
继续，敲击下一步。我们可以称呼我们的activity为 main activity。
Go ahead and click Next. We call our activity main activity. And the layout
我们会将布局写在 activity_main XML 文件里。
comes from the activity_main XML file. In similar fashion, the Fragments layout
同理，fragment 写在 fragment_main XML 里。继续，点击完成。
comes from the fragment_main XML file. Then we go ahead and hit Finish.
你应该把你创建的 Sunshine app 文件放在这里。
You should have your newly created Sunshine app with the files on the left here.
确保你的 Gradel Build 完成。
Make sure you wait for the Gradel Build to finish. If you still see errors,
当你看到有错误时，你可以点击下方 Guide and Instructor 字样，查看解决方案。
you can check the Guide and Instructor notes below on how to troubleshoot.
一个小窍门，你可以在Gradle文件源码中检查的 Min 和 Target SDK 版本。
As a tip, you can check your Min and Target SDK versions in the build out Gradle
我们希望编译的SDK版本和目标SDK版本，
file located under the app Source folder. We want the compile SDK version and
均为指向的该平台的最新版本表。
the target SDK version to point to the latest table version of the platform.
在这种情况下，它会是19，而不是 L.
In this case, it's 19 and not L. Once you have no errors,
一旦你有没有错误，我们可以添加更符合这个天气程序的自定义图标。
we can add a custom app icon that'll be more fitting for
在文件夹那单击右键，转到 New Image Asset。
our weather app. Right-click on the app folder and go to New Image Asset.
下载我们提供图标，继续，找到它。
Download the icon that we provide in the link below, then go ahead and
你可以在临时应用程序图标那进行预览。
find that icon. And here you can see a preview of our temporary app icon.
我们将会在未来做的更好。
We're going to get a better one in less than five. Then go ahead and
继续，点击完成。新的图标会显示在Drawable文件夹上。
click Next and Finish. And the new icon shows up in the Drawable folders.
好啦，自己动手试试吧！当然，你的步骤不能错，
Go ahead and try it yourself. Make sure you're using the same settings as we
你可以通过下面的链接进行检查。当你完成时，可以点这里。
have by checking the link below. Click here when you're done.